scrumwise.com 2019-01-31

# Scrumwise - Privacy policy

When you use our products and services, we may collect various pieces of information about you. This privacy policy explains what information we collect, how we collect the information, and how we use it. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, just ask us at [support@scrumwise.com](mailto:support@scrumwise.com). 

## Collected information

When you communicate with us via email or live chat, we may collect your name and email address. When you register as a user of our products and services, we may ask you to provide information such as your name, email address, company name, billing information, VAT number, and credit card information. 

## Use of the information

Scrumwise uses the information we collect from you for these purposes: communication with you; providing our products and services to you; authentication and authorization; billing; prevention of illegal activities, fraud, and violations of our terms of service; and research to improve our products and services. 

You may opt out of communication from us from within the products and services in which the information was collected, or by contacting us at [support@scrumwise.com](mailto:support@scrumwise.com). 

Scrumwise does not share the collected information with third parties, or otherwise disclose the collected information, unless you give us explicit permission to do so, or we are required by law to do so. 

We may transfer the collected information to another company if Scrumwise is acquired by or merged with another company. 

## Rights to the information

You retain all rights to the information that we collect from you. You may modify or delete the collected information if it is inaccurate at any time. You can do so from within the products or services in which the information was collected, or by contacting us at [support@scrumwise.com](mailto:support@scrumwise.com). 

## Storage of the information

Scrumwise uses third party vendors, hosting providers, and other service providers to provide the necessary software, hardware, network, storage, hosting environment, and other technologies to run our products and services. As part of that, we may use the services provided by those third parties to securely store the information that we collect from you. The collected credit card information is securely stored and accessed in compliance with the PCI DSS requirements. 

## Use of cookies

A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your computer from a website and stored on your computer, either for the duration of your session on the website, or permanently. A cookie often includes an anonymous unique id. 

We require the use of session cookies to use our products and services, but we do not require use of permanent cookies. 

As you browse our website at www.scrumwise.com, advertising cookies may be placed on your computer. This is done so that we can use advertising partners, such as Google, to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with our website. This allows us to spend as little money as possible on advertising, and as much money as possible on developing great products and services. 

Here are some of the keywords for which you may see advertising from us on other sites: Scrum tools, Scrum software, Scrum boards, Scrum project management tools, Scrum project management software, agile tools, agile software, agile project management tools, and agile project management software. 

The techniques our partners use do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, or telephone number. 

You can visit the following pages to opt out of targeted advertising from our advertising partners: 

## Changes to this policy

We may periodically update this privacy policy. If we make significant changes to the policy, we will notify you by sending an email to the contact person of the company account that your user account belongs to in Scrumwise, or by placing a prominent note on our website or blog.
